<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<link rel="self" href="http://drawaes.github.io/CondenserDocs" />
	<id>http://drawaes.github.io/CondenserDocs</id>
	<title />
	<rights>2017</rights>
	<updated>2017-08-12T21:00:36Z</updated>
	<entry>
		<author>
			<name>Tim Seaward</name>
		</author>
		<link href="http://drawaes.github.io/CondenserDocs/blog/catching-up" />
		<id>http://drawaes.github.io/CondenserDocs/blog/catching-up</id>
		<title>Catching up, from being a bit slack</title>
		<updated>2017-08-12T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<content>&lt;p&gt;I haven't blogged about releases in a while. For that I am sorry, there have been releases on going, including patches and more features like maintaince mode, de-registration and many more that I have forgotten. There are release notes for them all.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have improved the testing coverage of the things that are important a lot and have been working with some people using it in large environments to iron out some bugs. But now things are looking good. I have some plans, minor enhancements that I have added issues for but the reverse proxy is where there will be a lot of focus coming.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If anyone wants to dig in and help that would be awesome, any area is welcome but especially these&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Another provider other than consul, zookeeper or redis? This will help prove out and find now issues around abstracting the provider&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;General help on the reverse proxy, I plan to change to doing this with ASP.NET Core 2.0 and then quickly moving to the abstractions they are building out there.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A json comparison engine for Swagger docs for doing API change validation and rules.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anyway keep hanging around, bring the bug reports, and PR's are always welcome.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cheers&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tim&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
		<summary>&lt;p&gt;I haven't blogged about releases in a while. For that I am sorry, there have been releases on going, including patches and more features like maintaince mode, de-registration and many more that I have forgotten. There are release notes for them all.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<author>
			<name>Tim Seaward</name>
		</author>
		<link href="http://drawaes.github.io/CondenserDocs/blog/server-progressing" />
		<id>http://drawaes.github.io/CondenserDocs/blog/server-progressing</id>
		<title>Patch 2.0.2</title>
		<updated>2017-03-06T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<content>&lt;p&gt;The first issue is the stripping of trailing names from the executing assembly should now be fixed with &amp;quot;.Host&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;.Library&amp;quot; and
so on all removed by default. You can configure the suffixes you would like removed through the ServiceManagerConfig object.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Next the server is going through a decent refactor with the useful middleware being brought into a single package and the
middleware that contains experimental links (mostly to pipelines) being put into a seperate package for those that don't
want to live on the bleeding edge.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some benchmarking has been done on the experimental client and the overhead of calling out is about 1/2 of the current overhead
so I look forward to doing some more work around that and setting up a proper benchmark scripted environment to allow the results
to be published in a continuous way.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am interested to hear your feedback, problems or feature requests so email me at seawardtim at gmail or file an issue and tell
me the good the bad or just what you would like.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;P.S. Dean is making some progress on a new &amp;quot;status&amp;quot; viewer for the proxy, and I am working on a packaged server so
if you have features you think would be great or samples/use cases you want covered please do shout out we are taking requests.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cheers&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tim&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
		<summary>&lt;p&gt;The first issue is the stripping of trailing names from the executing assembly should now be fixed with ".Host", ".Library" and
so on all removed by default. You can configure the suffixes you would like removed through the ServiceManagerConfig object.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<author>
			<name>Tim Seaward</name>
		</author>
		<link href="http://drawaes.github.io/CondenserDocs/blog/client-refactor" />
		<id>http://drawaes.github.io/CondenserDocs/blog/client-refactor</id>
		<title>Refactored the Client Libraries</title>
		<updated>2017-02-28T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<content>&lt;p&gt;There has been a pretty large refactor of the client libraries. As with any very early API it has taken some time using the library in the real
world to gain an understanding of what works and what doesn't. This has shown that the current API for registering your services required
a lot of boilerplate code. Also if you wanted to change a single setting it required you to set a lot of settings you would like to leave it as
the defaults.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We also realised that is was becoming difficult to test various parts of the system and when you only wanted to use a single part (say you
wanted to find services but you didn't have a service to register yourself) you still required all of the parts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Currently the new API is complete for the Registration/Discovery part however we won't be doing an official release yet as we have some work
to do on the configuration. When the release is done we will likely move the client to 2.0.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a final part of the refactor we may move the API router out to a seperate repo and have it on its own path. This has yet to be confirmed.
Dean is also working on a SPA Gui to manage and view data and statistics from the API Router.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
		<summary>&lt;p&gt;There has been a pretty large refactor of the client libraries. As with any very early API it has taken some time using the library in the real
world to gain an understanding of what works and what doesn't. This has shown that the current API for registering your services required
a lot of boilerplate code. Also if you wanted to change a single setting it required you to set a lot of settings you would like to leave it as
the defaults.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<author>
			<name>Tim Seaward</name>
		</author>
		<link href="http://drawaes.github.io/CondenserDocs/blog/new-release" />
		<id>http://drawaes.github.io/CondenserDocs/blog/new-release</id>
		<title>Documentation started</title>
		<updated>2017-02-16T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<content>&lt;p&gt;We have started a new documentation site with a new Logo!&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
		<summary>&lt;p&gt;We have started a new documentation site with a new Logo!&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
	</entry>
</feed>